Guide to the Deedee Corradini audio-visual collection 1984-1999
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Deedee Corradini audio-visual collection
1984-1999
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 801-581-8864 http://www.lib.utah.edu/collections/multimedia-archives/
A0736
Corradini, Deedee
121 VHS videocassettes, 1 Betamax vieocassette, and 9 audiocassettes
The Deedee Corradini audio-visual collection (1984-1999) consists of mostly VHS cassettes relating to Corradini's two terms as mayor of Salt Lake City. Materials include election coverage of both elections, news clips, and various other related materials.
Biographical Note
Deedee Corradini was the first and to date only female mayor of Salt Lake City. She was instrumental in many important projects during her time as mayor (1992-2000) including but not limited to Salt Lake City's bid for the 2002 Winter Olympic Games, support of Trax public transportation in downtown, and the development of Gateway shopping center. She was also head of the US conference of mayors in 1998.
The Deedee Corradini audio-visual collection (1984-1999) consists of mostly VHS cassettes relating to Corradini's two terms as mayor of Salt Lake City. Materials include election coverage of both elections, news clips, and various other related materials.
Materials are arranged alphabetically by format.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Donated by Deedee Corradini in 2012.
See also the Deedee Corradini papers (Accn 2024) and photograph collection (P1445).
Salt Lake City (Utah); Mayors; Politics and culture--United States; Political Campaigns; Moving Images; Sound Recordings; Moving images; Sound recordings
- Box 1 (File 1)
  - Airport design, 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1)
  - "Airport master plan", 1997 March 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2)
  - Announcement, Kolls interview, KSL story, Kolls, 1991 June 4; 1991 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 3)
  - BAT news broadcast chronology, 1990 August-1993 January; VHS videocassette (Cassette 4)
  - Bike to work day Salt Lake City, 1998 May 13; VHS videocassette (Cassette 5)
  - The Bloomberg forum Salt Lake City Deedee Corradini, Mayor interview, 1998 July 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 6)
  - Bowlmania, 1984 January 7; VHS videocassette (Cassette 7)
  - Buhler, Jones, Zuhl announcements, 1991 May; VHS videocassette (Cassette 8)
  - Bull Session, 1997 March 7; VHS videocassette (Cassette 9)
  - Calgary '88 16 days of glory part II, 1988; VHS videocassette (Cassette 10)
  - CBS This Morning, 1994 February 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 11)
  - CBS this morning Salt Lake City 2002, 1998 February 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 12)
  - Colorado incident/Salt Lake City mayor, 1999 April 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 13)
  - Columbus, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 14)
  - A conversation with Deedee Corradini, 1999 October; VHS videocassette (Cassette 15)
  - Corradini, Deedee – KSL interview, 1993 May; VHS videocassette (Cassette 16)
  - Corradini for Mayor 1 – Action, 2 – Kids, 3 – Mom, 1995 September 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 17)
  - Corradini news clips, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 18)
  - Corradini/McKeown debate KSL, 1995 October 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 19)
  - Corradini off the record, 1993 May 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 20)
  - Corradini Presidency: Year of our youth, 2 copies, 1999 June; VHS videocassette (Cassette 21)
  - Crime bill signing, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 22)
  - Curbside recycling, 1993 April 7; VHS videocassette (Cassette 23)
  - Death at Oceanside Park, Undated; Betamax (Cassette 24)
  - Deedee announcement channels 2 and 5, 1991 June 4; VHS videocassette (Cassette 25)
  - Deedee at RSC (illegible), Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 26)
  - Deedee – CBS night watch, 1991 November 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 27)
  - Deedee – Ch.5 post election, Deedee – CBS night watch, 1991 November 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 28)
  - Deedee Corradini, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 29)
  - Deedee Corradini 1x:30, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 30)
  - Deedee Corradini 4x:30, 2 copies, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 31)
- Box 2 (File 2)
  - Deedee Corradini, 1991 August 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 32)
  - Deedee Corradini airport channel spots, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 33)
  - Deedee Corradini for mayor "chair", 1995 October 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 34)
  - Deedee Corradini for mayor "couple", 1995 October 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 35)
  - Deedee Corradini national plan on youth violence fox news channel, 1998 October 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 36)
  - Deedee Corradini speaks on metropolitan economies, 2 copies, 1998 December 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 37)
  - Deedee 1996 Debate, 1995 October 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 38)
  - Deedee dub, 1994 September 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 39)
  - Deedee press conference, 1992 June 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 40)
  - Deedee swearing-in, 1992 January 6; VHS videocassette (Cassette 41)
  - Deedee Today, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 42)
  - Disertacion de la Alcaldesa Deedee Corradini, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 43)
  - Election news Deedee, 1991; VHS videocassette (Cassette 44)
  - Endorsement DC-04 Deedee for mayor, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 45)
  - The dream comes true, 2002; VHS videocassette (Cassette 46)
  - Fox mayoral debate, 1995 October 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 47)
  - "Franklin Quest Field", 1996 April 4; VHS videocassette (Cassette 48)
  - From New York to Portland "looking back and moving forward", 1993-1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 49)
  - "The future is now" A Salt Lake City youth city government video, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 50)
  - The game goes on, 1994 April 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 51)
  - "Gateway project", 1997 April 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 52)
  - Good Morning America, 1991 July 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 53)
  - Good Morning America Mayor Deedee Corradini on Salt Lake City olympics, 2 copies, 1999 January 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 54)
  - Governor/mayor interviews CBS network, 1994 February 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 55)
  - "Inside Politics" with Mayor Corradini, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 56)
  - The James Brown Show "Mayors", 1997 November; VHS videocassette (Cassette 57)
  - "Janet Reno" Larry King Live, 1999 April 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 58)
  - KSL 6pm KTVX 10pm "Mayors meet in Washington", Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 59)
  - KSL 6pm Jay Kolls re: Finances, Phil Rirsen Panel, Rod Doricon, KSL profile, 1991 September 24; 1991 September 29; 1991 October 2; VHS videocassette (Cassette 60)
  - KUTV, KUED Deedee press conference, 1992 June 23; 1991 June 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 61)
  - Lessons Deedee Corradini, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 62)
- Box 3 (File 3)
  - Light rail transit – one component of an integrated transit system, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 63)
  - Lillehammer '94 16 days of glory, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 64)
  - Lillehammer '94 16 days of glory part II, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 65)
  - Local news segments on UP and L pres. resignation, 1987 February 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 66)
  - Management services total quality assessment presentation, 1997 April 9; VHS videocassette (Cassette 67)
  - March of Dimes – gourmet gala, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 68)
  - "Martin Luther King Jr. Blvd.", Fleet, 1993 August 10; 1993 August 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 69)
  - Master plan copy SLCAA – 2 copies, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 70)
  - Mayor Corradini Engaged, 3 copies, 1999 June 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 71)
  - Mayor Corradini is married, 1999 November 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 72)
  - Mayor Deedee Corradini early edition Cable News Network 2/12/99, 1999 February 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 73)
  - Mayor Deedee Corradini's late night basketball league all-star game, 2 copies, 1992 August 1; VHS videocassette (Cassette 74)
  - Mayor Deedee Corradini's press conference and interview, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 75)
  - Mayor Deedee Corradini speech at leadership Louisville, 1994 April 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 76)
  - "Mayor meets with Clinton Administration", 2 copies, 1998 May 8; VHS videocassette (Cassette 77)
  - Mayoral Candidates, 1991 March 7; VHS videocassette (Cassette 78)
  - "Mayoral Race", 1997 April 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 79)
  - Mayors' olympikids for fitness, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 80)
  - McNeil-Lehrer, Mayors – unfunded mandates, 1995 January 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 81)
  - Mean Streets SLC gangs, 1989 July 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 82)
  - MGMT 4950 executive lecture series Dr. Christopher G. Jones, Deedee Corradini, 2003 September 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 83)
  - Nagano '98 Olympics Stories of Honor and Glory, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 84)
  - Newsmakers Saturday, 2 copies, 1993 December 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 85)
  - Nightly business report, 1992 March 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 86)
  - Niketown Boston "Thursday night running club", 1998 March; VHS videocassette (Cassette 87)
  - The Olympic Games in the world's second home, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 88)
  - Olympics: Nagano closing ceremony, SLC – arrival of flag, news story, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 89)
  - Olympikids in Oakland 3/22/99, 1999 March 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 90)
  - Race for mayor – Steve Harmsen, Doug Foxley, 1995 June 5; 1995 June 13; VHS videocassette (Cassette 91)
  - Salt Lake City and County building: "For another century" 7/11/91, 1991 July 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 92)
  - Salt Lake City bid for the 1998 winter games, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 93)
  - Salt Lake City mayor's office news clips, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 94)
  - Salt Lake City "once upon a time", 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 95)
- Box 4 (File 4)
  - "Secretary of Transportation Slater visits Utah", 1997 November 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 96)
  - SLC Mayor, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 97)
  - SL Mayors recycling committee Albertsons generic, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 98)
  - SLC Mayor TV news coverage 1 of 3, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 99)
  - SLC Mayor TV news coverage 2 of 3, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 100)
  - SLC Mayor TV news coverage 3 of 3, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 101)
  - SLOC Olympic emblem story, 1997 August 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 102)
  - Specialist for a day: SLC Mayor Deedee Corradini, SLC Mayor's attorney in Wash. DC., 1993 November 12; 1995 May 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 103)
  - Sterling Scholars presenters tape, 1993 April 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 104)
  - Take action America on America's Voice, 1999 April 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 105)
  - Travelers Aid Society "Benihana Celebrity Chef", 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 106)
  - The United States Conference of Mayors "A salute to our presidents", 1995 June 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 107)
  - U.S. Conference of Mayors, olympikids, dancing in the streets, 3 copies, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 108)
  - U.S. Conference of Mayors summer fitness olympikids, 5 copies, 1999 May 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 109)
  - USOC Presentation with Salt Lake revision, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 110)
  - Utah Winter Olympics "Higher ground", Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 111)
  - Westin Hotels in Salt Lake City, 1996 March 8; VHS videocassette (Cassette 112)
  - Wirth Watching: Franklin Quest Field, Wirth Watching: Franklin Quest Field, 1993 October 13; 1994 March 2; VHS videocassette (Cassette 113)
  - KUED, 1995 October 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 114)
  - 1995 Mayor's Race, VHS videocassette (Cassette 115)
  - "2002 Olympics/Salt Lake City" Mayor Deedee Corradini, 1996 May 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 116)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 117)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 118)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 119)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 120)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 121)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 122)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 123)
  - Unlabeled, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 124)
  - Amanda Dixon KSL, 1991 May 5; Audiocassette (Cassette 1)
  - Corradini for mayor "Headlines", Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 2)
  - Deedee Corradini for mayor "Headlines", 1991 September; Audiocassette (Cassette 3)
  - Deedee Corradini for mayor "Testimonial", 1991 October; Audiocassette (Cassette 4)
  - Deedee K-Talk radio, 1991 April 22; Audiocassette (Cassette 5)
  - Deedee radio spot – please return, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 6)
  - Executive/entrepreneur lecture Deedee Corradini, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 7)
  - Talk America radio network "America good morning", 1984 September 24; Audiocassette (Cassette 8)
  - Talk of the nation mayor roundtable, 1998 August 3; Audiocassette (Cassette 9)
  - Youth fitness event in Oakland, CA, 1999 March 22; Audiocassette (Cassette 10)